Celine Roure

Melbourne celine.r@mail.com 0424 000 000

I am aspiring to become Web-developer

Friendly and supportive team player, I am passionate about solving problems. After being a full-time mum for almost three years, I am ready for new challenges and get all the chances I can for a successful career change. With a background in marketing, I would like to use this knowledge and evolve into a more technical job. I am super motivated to start this new journey!

Work experience

2017- 2018 Early Childhood Educator

River Garden From 1 to 2 years old's room

Early Learning Supervised and interact effectively with children in open spaces areas

Guardian Group Developed a positive and respectful relationships with children and families

South yarra, VIC Provided creative and natural experiences to support children's learning based on

children's interests

Cared in health and hygiene, maintained the room safe

Participated in food serving

Participated in daily reflections and observations on Storypark

Accompanied Children to excursions

2015-2016 Early Childhood Educator

Woodland Education In Toddler room

Early Learning Supervised and interact effectively with children

Guardian Group Developed a positive and respectful relationships with children and families

Melbourne, VIC Followed the room's routine and participated in the room's program Participated weekly in learning stories and daily reflections on Xplor

Provided experiences to support children's learning based on children's interests,

Initiated daily physical, musical or artistic learning experiences

2013 - 2011 Insurance Claims Processor

Pacifica Department specialised in agriculture.

Crédit Agricole Group Gained comprehensive knowledge of agricultural insurance policy

Montpellier, France Processed Recording claims by telephone and mail.

Validated claims and contracts using current applicable guidelines and executed risk evaluation through effective investigation and follow-up.

Evaluation of damage and taking decisions to send an expert.

Analysis of expert reports and payments (up to \$22K) while applying the appropriate reimbursement when due, audits, and assigned tasks.

2010

Groupe Y.Perez Montpellier, France

Marketing and Administration Assistant

For 5 brands specialised in professional Cosmetics products.

Analysed market and business opportunities.

Analysed sales report weekly and managed the stock Managed customer product returns and exchanges

Elaborated communication and promotion.

Participated in designing and arranging window displays. Organised and representative in trade exhibitions in Paris.

2008-2006 CANDILLON-RABEC Alès. France Client Services Representative

Insurance broker

Thorough knowledge of terms and conditions for 5 different companies Conferred with customers by telephone or in person in order to provide

information about products and services

Produced guotes for home contracts, automobile contracts

Subscription insurance policies

Education

Diploma of I.T (in progress)

Coder Academy, Melbourne, VIC 2021

Certificate 3 in Early Childhood Education and Care

Melbourne Polytechnic, Preston, VIC, 2015

Master of Marketing and Sales Management

Montpellier Management, France, 2010

Diploma in Insurance

Nîmes University - Nîmes, France, 2007

Others

Certificates of Completion:

HTML, CSS, Responsive Layout,

Command Line

Code Academy 2020 Linkedin Learning 2020

CPR

Stitches First Aid Education, VIC, Sept 2017

First Aid Certificate, Anaphylaxis and Asthma management training

Melbourne Polytechnic, Preston, VIC, August 2015

Interests

Reading, education, feminism, Hiking, sustainability, DIY, gardening

Reference

Upon request